Guide to the Cornell University Library Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections records, 1992-2015.
Cornell University Library Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections records, 1992-2015.
- Margaret Nichols files (Box 212)
- Request slips (Box 213)
- RBMS tee shirts and tote bags (2 of each) (Box 214)
- Margaret Nichols files (ca. 2000-2010) (Box 215)
- Permissions 1990-2008 (Box 216)
- Request slips (Box 217-221)
- RBMS/office files, 2003-2011 (Box 222)
- Margaret Nichols files, 1997-2011 (Box 223)
- Nancy Dean files: ref questions and miscellaneous (Box 224)
- Margaret Nichols files, 2006-2015 (Box 225)
- New accessions Part I, II, III (Box 226)
  Pre-excel list
- Annual report stats, 2009 (Box 226, Folder 1)
- Archives video tape accessions, Undated (Box 226, Folder 2)
- Donor correspondence A-D, 1988, 1994-1996 (Box 226, Folder 3)
- Donor correspondence E-K, 1993-1999 (Box 226, Folder 4)
- Donor correspondence L-O, 1990-1997 (Box 226, Folder 5)
- Donor correspondence P-Z, 1993-1997 (Box 226, Folder 6)
- Nancy Dean files: genealogy resources (Box 227)
- Vault and mezzanine sign-in sheets (Box 228)
- Exhibit material (Mapcase-folder 1)
- Archives Manuscript Collection stickers from carts used during move to Kroch Library from Olin Library, 1992 (Folder Mss. Folder)
- Video V-165